<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes" ?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Poetries on Morgan Hayes</title>
    <link>http://morganhayes.org/poetry/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Poetries on Morgan Hayes</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Sat, 05 Nov 2016 19:53:42 +0530</lastBuildDate>
    
	<atom:link href="http://morganhayes.org/poetry/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    
    
    <item>
      <title>Ignite</title>
      <link>http://morganhayes.org/poetry/work5/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 05 Nov 2016 19:53:42 +0530</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://morganhayes.org/poetry/work5/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;The embers of our childhood are cold and grey,
Memories of those we lost, carried day by day.
We grew up far too fast, our hearts became tough.
But we have found our time, and enough is enough.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;We are a spark and you are a sea of darkness,
Extinguishing our light, hideous and heartless.
Your money is stained with the blood of our youth,
The generation that taught us the importance of truth.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Now, just a front for sanctimonious swine,
Who censor all that does not fit their design,
Who ban books but not guns, because think of the children.
And happily send them to the place they’ll be killed in.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Save your thoughts, your prayers, and your amen.
Did those help when we were killed time and again?
Don’t pretend your muttered consolations,
Mean more than actual laws and gun regulations.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;As if a child’s glow being snuffed out,
Doesn’t mean as much as the amendment you spout.
As if your privilege to own a gun,
Outranks my freedom to not die from one.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;You turn our schools into dread,
You leave us riddled with lead,
You ignore all that we’ve pled,
You won’t even look at our dead.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;And we will not take it.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Not from you, who’s fault is this crime.
Those who forced us to mature before our time,
Who say we can’t have opinions about our own onslaught,
Like we’re too young to be shot.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;We are standing up for ourselves, since nobody else will,
And all the others you’ve let your inaction kill.
This is the pain your regime has wrought,
This is the legacy your blood money has bought.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;We are armed. Not with weapons, lies, or mockery.
We are armed with courage, compassion, camaraderie.
Against the monumental resistance from all ends,
We will fight for peace, to avenge our fallen friends.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;And, in this oppressive night, we’ve finally been set ablaze.
As It takes true darkness to finally see light,
It takes a breath to burn the brightest,
and a single spark can ignite a revolution.&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>